{
    "id": "dc2f48f4e0d74efdb621ba59c9cfb156",
    "title": "Adverb Clause Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I waited for my friend ......................................... he arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "up to",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "76a9ce7a9c08431ea028ae3c8d41dfd8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He hid ......................................... his pursuers could not find him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "where",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a94128674acf433f979b45fb8d91694a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am as intelligent ....................................... you are.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "09067774b8454c75af21b34481a4ffa5"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................ he was not there, I left a message with his mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "So",
                "Therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b76cffb697b3447ebc919e76fa006db6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We eat .............................................. we may live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "so",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "163d130e3387414b96ba46c66241d056"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ........................................... tired that she could barely stand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7120854196744de48fc8efc8355f7277"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................................. you eat too much, you may fall ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e7427c07a6d4e7592f086e20684e818"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ he started early, he finished late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "So"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7cd354356040433480f797ccc9f49b7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................... you do not tell me everything, I will not be able to help you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "556947bc872e459bbf63d8809c93a880"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not go ................................................ I get ready.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "unless",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5ba103347c7b4864b626e5bea02136e6"
        }
    ]
}